DeBella, Anthony Collection of Rome, NY, Labor Union Materials 6311
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Anthony DeBella Collection of Rome, NY, Labor Union Materials
1936-1949
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Debella, Anthony
6311
0.83 cubic feet
0.8 linear ft.
Records.
This material includes agreements, constitutions, by-laws, correspondence, and organizing materials and two large scrapbooks of newspaper clippings.
7181314
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Biographical / Historical
The Interstate Copper and Brass Workers' Union was affiliated with CUA, then MESA.
Scope and Contents
This material includes agreements, constitutions, by-laws, correspondence, and organizing materials and two large scrapbooks of newspaper clippings.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: #5679 Mechanics Educational Society of America Rome City Central Records 1939-1970 (MESA)
Metal-workers--Labor unions; DeBella, Anthony; General Cable Corporation; Independent Interstate Copper and Brass Workers' Union; Interstate Copper and Brass Workers' Union; Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated; Revere Copper and Brass Independent Employees' Union. Rome Division; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
7181314
- Revere Copper and Brass, Inc. and the Revere Copper and Brass Independent Employees. Revere Copper and Brass, Inc. and the Interstate Copper and Brass Workers Union.. Revere Copper and Brass, Inc. and the Independent Interstate Copper and Brass Workers (Box 1)
  - MESA Nat. Office, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Important Interstate & MESA Merger Correspondence
  - Rare CUA Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Envelope - Confederated Unions of America 1940's
  - Constitution of Ibero-Americana, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Important War Labor Board Material, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Envelope - 1940's
  - Rare Interstate Union Documents, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    1940's
  - Financial Reports of Independent Interstate Copper & Brass Workers Union, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Independent Interstate Copper & Brass Workers Union Annual Conventions, 1939-1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Old Documents (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NLRB Proceeding Revere Copper & Brass - Interstate Union & UECIO (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - UECIO - Leaflets & Other Documents, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Envelope - General Cable Corp. 1940's, General Cable Guild & Interstate Metal Worker Union
  - General Cable Guild, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Interstate Union Revere Copper & Brass, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Independent Revere Union, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Interstate Union, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cable Guild (General Cable - Rome Plant), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    General Cable Guild, Interstate Copper & Brass Worker Union & UECIO
  - Brass & Copper Industrial Council, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Meeting Minutes Independent Interstate Copper & Brass Workers Union, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Booklets (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Two large scrapbooks of newspaper clippings.. (Box 2)
  - MESA Clippings (Miscellaneous), 1936-1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Large Scrapbook
  - AFL Clippings, etc., 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)